## **Madhavi Patel**

Lansdale, PA 19446 • 267-421-9854 • Madhavip122@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/madhavip93

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Energetic and creative marketing candidate focused on positively impacting business goals and improving customer relations. A team player with top-notch communication skills, strong ability to solve problems, experience in social media, and a desire to continually learn and advance my abilities and skills within the field of Digital Marketing.

### **EDUCATION**

Master of Science in Marketing
Concentration in New Media and Communications
Southern New Hampshire University
December 2020

Bachelor of Science - Elementary Education Pre K-4th
Penn State University
December 2016

### **KEY SKILLS**

- Google AnalyticsSEO
- Content Marketing 

   Adobe Creative Suite, Canva
- Google Ads Certified

   Wix, Mail Chimp, Hootsuite, WordPress
- Microsoft Office Suite Quick book

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Digital Marketing Intern June 2020-August 2020

Onpoint Success, King Of Prussia, Philadelphia, PA

Advanced Social Media Knowledge

- Curated social media content and email campaigns through Mail Chimp/Hootsuite
- Improvised various social media platforms
- Tracked and responded to customer reviews online
- Created Graphics and logos with Canva

## Digital Marketing Intern May 2019-August 2019

Holiday Inn Express & Suites, Clear Spring, MD

- Supervised social media websites and third party reservations
- Tracked and responded to customer reviews online
- Crafted graphics and logos for the hotel

### **Public Relations, Marketing, and Communications Intern**

The Gabriel Institute, Philadelphia, PA

- Conducted various research projects
- Created blog content through Wordpress
- Drafted a press kit and a new page for the company's website through Wix
- In charge of Company's tweets and Facebook posts.

#### **Instructional Para Professional**

September 2017- Current

Skippack Elementary, Collegeville, PA

- Analyzed student academic progress and create reports for teachers and administrators on a weekly basis
- Utilized data from standardized exams to guide instruction and intervention
- Used graphics, work samples, and reports to give feedback to parents about student progress
- Utilized software such PowerPoint, Flipboard, and iMovie to create lessons that are visually appealing and provide necessary information in a memorable way.

June 2018-August 2018

# **Social Media Leader/Mentor**

Holiday Inn Express & Suites, Exmore, VA

August 2016-August 2017

- Led quarterly presentations demonstrating online aspect of the hotel
- Monitored social media websites and third party reservation websites
- Mentored and shared insightful ideas to satisfy customers and increase revenue goals
- Tracked and responded to customer reviews online